Guide to the Charles Hamm Recordings, 1857-1999 HAMM.2005
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Charles Hamm Collection
1857-1999
1960-1980
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Hamm, Charles
HAMM.2005
13 Linear Feet (678 Albums)
This collection consists of 678 record albums ranging in genre from Rock & Roll to Classical. It was acquired over time by Dr. Charles Hamm during his career as a musicologist and professor of music. The collection represents the wide variety and scope of American music through the early- to late-twentieth century.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically into 13 series; each series is broken into item level descriptions for each album.
Series I. Classical (CAL)
Series II. Country (CON)
Series III. Early Parlor Songs (EPS)
Series IV. Eastern European (EUR)
Series V. Folk (FLK)
Series VI. Foster (FOS)
Series VII. Gospel (GOS)
Series VIII. Jazz (JAZ)
Series IX. Popular (POP)
Series X. Radio (RAD)
Series XI. Ragtime (RAG)
Series XII. Soundtracks (SDT)
Series XIII. Soul (SOL)
Acquisition Information
This collection was gifted to The Center for American Music Stephen Foster Hall Archives by Dr. Charles Hamm in 2005.
Biography
Dr. Charles Edward Hamm was born in Charlottesville, Va., on April 21, 1925. In 1947, he graduated from the University of Virginia with a BA in music. Dr. Hamm went on to earn his MFA in 1950 and his PhD in musicology from Princeton University in 1960. He taught at Princeton, the Cincinnati Conservatory of Music, Tulane University, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, and Dartmouth College. Dr. Hamm was also president of the American Musicological Society from 1972-1974. He retired professionally in 1989.
Reflected in the scope of his sound recording collection, Dr. Hamm focused his studies on twentieth century popular American music, publishing many journal articles and books on the subject. His writings later in his career delved more deeply into the growing use of mass media in late-twentieth century musical styles and rituals, and the intercultural reception of music.
Scope and Content Notes
The Charles Hamm Recordings are housed in individual record sleeves. Most of the sleeves are the original record album covers. The records are housed standing vertically on the shelf space so as to reduce wear and warping of the LPs. Each series in this collection consists of individual LPs with various artists. The records are arranged into thirteen series.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Phonograph records; Sound recordings -- Collectors and collecting -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Sound recording libraries -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Music
- Recordings on LP, 1
  - Soul, 1967-1978; XIII.
    Scope and Content Notes
    This series consists of 13 albums. These albums represent the American Popular music of Soul.
    - Marvin Gaye: I Want You, 1976 (Record HAMM SOL 0001)
      This album includes I want you (vocal) -- Come live with me angel -- After the dance (instrumental) -- Feel all my love inside -- I wanna be where you are -- I want you (intro jam) -- All the way around -- Since I had you -- Soon I'll be loving you again -- I want you (intro jam) -- After the dance (vocal).
    - Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five: Greatest, 1984 (Record HAMM SOL 0002)
      This album includes Freedom -- Birthday party -- Flash to the beat -- It's nasty -- Message -- Scorpio -- Survival (Message II) -- New York, New York.
    - Isaac Hayes: Hot Buttered Soul, 1969 (Record HAMM SOL 0003)
      This album includes Walk on by (12:00, BMI) - Hyperbolicsyllabicsesquedalymistic (9:55, ASCAP) - One woman (5:00, BMI) - By The Time I Get To Phoenix (18:40, BMI).
    - Gladys Knight and the Pips: Anthology, 1973 (Record HAMM SOL 0004)
      This album includes Every beat of my heart -- Letter full of tears -- Giving up -- Just walk in my shoes -- Take me in your arms and love me -- Everybody needs love -- I heard it through the grapevine -- The end of our road -- It should have been me -- I wish it would rain -- Didn't you know (you'd have to cry sometime) -- The nitty gritty -- Friendship train -- The tracks of my tears -- You need love like I do (don't you) -- Every little bit hurts -- If I were your woman -- I don't want to do wrong -- Make me the woman that you go home to -- Help me make it through the night -- For once in my life -- Neither of us (wants to be the first to say goodbye) -- Daddy could swear, I declare.
    - Harold Melvin and The Blue Notes: Reaching For The World, 1976 (Record HAMM SOL 0005)
      This album includes Reaching for the world -- Where there's a will, there's a way -- After you love me, why do you leave me -- Sandman -- Hostage part 1 & 2 -- He loves you and I do too -- Big singing star -- Stay together.
    - Teddy Pendergrass: Life is a Song Worth Singing, 1978 (Record HAMM SOL 0006)
      This album includes Life is a song worth singing -- Only you -- Cold, cold world -- Get up, get down, get funky, get loose -- Close the door -- It don't hurt now -- When somebody loves you back.
    - Otis Rush: Cold Day in Hell, 1975 (Record HAMM SOL 0007)
      This album includes Cut you loose -- You're breaking my heart -- Midnight Special -- Society woman -- Mean old world -- All your love I miss loving; Jam -- Cold day in hell -- Motoring along.
    - Pharoah Sanders: Deaf dumb blind, 1970 (Record HAMM SOL 0008)
      This album includes Summun Bukmun Umyun (21:24) - Let Us Go Into The House Of The Lord (17:52).
    - The Dynamic O.C. Smith, 1967 (Record HAMM SOL 0009)
      This album includes On a clear day you can see forever -- That's life -- My romance -- Work song -- On the southside of Chicago -- Fever -- The season -- Georgia rose -- Quiet nights of quiet stars -- What now my love -- Here's that rainy day.
    - Edwin Starr, War & Peace, 1970 (Record HAMM SOL 0010)
      This album includes War -- Running back and forth -- Adios senorita -- All around the world -- I can't escape your memory -- At last (I found a love) -- I just wanted to cry -- Raindrops keep fallin' on my head -- Time -- California soul -- I can't replace my old love -- She should have been home.
    - The Temptations: The Temptations Show, 1969 (Record HAMM SOL 0011)
      This album includes Opening-- Get ready (2:43) -- Medley. Girl (why you wanna' make me blue); Beauty is only skin deep; You're my everything; My girl; Ain't too proud to beg (5:05) -- Temptations introduction (:35) -- I've got to be me (2:33) -- Cloud nine (3:07) -- For once in my life (Kay Stevens) (2:55) -- Try it baby (the Temptations & Kay Stevens) (2:40) -- When I lay my burdens down (George Kirby) (6:12) -- Medley. The best things in life are free; Life (2:03) -- Monologue and medley. Ol' man river; Swanee; Old folks (5:11) -- Comedy routine. Hello young lovers; Cloud nine; If I didn't care (the Temptations & George Kirby) (5:09) -- Runaway child, running wild (3:06) -- Finale. Somebody's keepin' score.
    - The World of Ike and Tina, 1973 (Record HAMM SOL 0012)
      This album includes Theme from "Shaft" -- I gotcha -- Intro to Tina -- She came in through the bathroom window -- You're still my baby -- Don't fight it -- Annie had a baby -- With a little help from my friends -- Get back -- Games people play -- Honky tonk women -- If you love me like you say -- I can't turn you loose -- I wish it would rain -- Just one more day -- Stand by me -- Dust my broom -- River deep, mountain high -- Let me touch your mind -- Chopper -- 1-2-3.
    - The Watts 103rd Street Rhythm Band: Together, 1968 (Record HAMM SOL 0013)
      This album includes Sorry Charlie -- Something you got -- 65 bars and a taste of soul -- Papa's got a brand new bag -- (I can't get no) satisfaction -- A dance, a kiss and a song -- Phuncky Bill -- Get ready -- Stormy Monday -- Giggin' down 103rd -- My summer's gone -- Knock on wood -- I wake up crying -- Do your thing.
  - Soundtracks, 1952-1987; XII.
    This series consists of 16 albums. These albums represent musical soundtracks from a variety of stage shows and movies.
    - A Chorus Line (Original Cast Recording), 1975 (Record HAMM SDT 0001)
      This album includes I hope I get it (Company) - I can do that (Mike /Wayne Cilento) - At the Ballet (Sheila, Bebe, Maggie /Carole Bishop, Nancy Lane, Kay Cole) - Sing! (Kristine, Al /Renee Baughman, Don Percassi) - Hello twelve, Hello thirteen, Hello Love (Montage) (Company) - Nothing (Diana /Priscilla Lopez) - The music and the mirror (Cassie /Donna McKechnie) - Dance: Ten; Looks: Three (Val /Pamela Blair) - One (Company) - What I did for love (Diana and Company /Priscilla Lopez) - One (Reprise)-Finale (Company).
    - Fiddler on the Roof: The Original Broardway Cast Recording, 1964 (Record HAMM SDT 0002)
      This album includes Tradition -- Matchmaker, matchmaker -- If I were a rich man -- Sabbath prayer -- To life -- Miracle of miracles -- Tevye's dream -- Sunrise, sunset -- Now I have everything -- Do you love me? -- Far from the home I love -- Anatevka.
    - Nelson Eddy in Oklahoma (Record HAMM SDT 0003)
      This album includes Overture - Opening of Act 1: Oh, what a beautiful mornin' - The surrey with the Fringe on top - Kansas city - I can't say no - Entrance of ensemble - Many a new day - It's a sacnadal!It's a outrage! - People will say we're in love - Pore Jud is daid - Lonely room - Out of my dreams - Opening of Act II. The farmer and the cowman - All er nothin'.
    - Jerome Kern's Roberta: Lovely to Look At, 1952 (Record HAMM SDT 0004)
      This album includes Lovely to look at -- Let's begin -- Yesterdays -- The touch of your hand -- (When your heart's on fire) Smoke get in your eyes -- I won't dance -- You're devastating -- I'll be hard to handle.
    - Angela Lansbury as "Mame", 1966 (Record HAMM SDT 0005)
      This album includes Overture (Orchestra) - St. Bridget (Connell, Michaels) - It's today (Lansbury and All) - Open a new window (Lansbury and All) - The man in the moon (Arthur, Lansbury and Maidens) - My best girl (Michaels, Landsbury) - We need a little Christmas (Lansbury, Michaels, Connell, Shimono) - Mame (Braswell and All) - The Letter (Michaels, Lanning) - Bosom Buddies (Lansbury, Arther) - Gooch's song (Connell) - That's how young I feel (Lansbury and All) - If he walked into my life (Lansbury) - Finale (Lansbury and All).
    - Jeanette MacDonald and Nelson Eddy Favorites in HI_FI, 1959 (Record HAMM SDT 0006)
      This album includes Will you remember (Sweetheart) (Duet) - Rosalie (Nelson Eddy) - Giannina Mia (Jeanette MacDonald) - Rose-Marie (Nelson Eddy) - Italian Street Song (Jeanette MacDonald - Indian love call (Duet) - Ah, Sweet mystery of love (duet) - The breeze and I (Jeanette MacDonald - While my lady sleeps (Nelson eddy) - Wanting you (Duet) - Stouthearted men (Nelson Eddy) - Beyond the blue horizon (Jeanette MacDonald).
    - Easy Rider, 1969 (Record HAMM SDT 0007)
      This album includes The pusher (Steppenwolf) - Born to be wild (Steppenwolf) - The weight (Smith) - Wasn't born to follow (The Byrds) - If you want to be a bird (The Holy Modal Rouners) - Don't bogart me (Fratenity of Man) - If six was nine (The Jimi Hendrix experience) - Kyrie Eleison (The Electic Prunes) - It's alright ma (I'm only bleeding) (Roger McGuinn) - Ballad of easy rider (Roger McGuinn).
    - Dirty Dancing Soudtrack, 1987 (Record HAMM SDT 0008)
      This album includes (I've had) The time of my life (Bill Medley, Jennifer Warnes) -- Be my baby (the Ronettes) -- She's like the wind (Patrick Swayze) -- Hungry eyes (Eric Carmen) -- Stay (Maurice Williams and the Zodiacs) -- Yes (Merry Clayton) -- You don't own me (the Blow Monkeys) -- Hey baby (Bruce Channel) -- Overload (Zappacosta) -- Love is strange (Mickey and Sylvia) -- Where are you tonight (Tom Johnston) -- In the still of the night (the Five Satins).
    - Jesus Christ Superstar: A Rock Opera, 1970 (Record HAMM SDT 0009)
      This album includes Overture - Heaven on their minds - What's the buzz/strange things mystifying - Everything's alright - This Jesus must die - Hosanna - simon Zealotes/Poor Jerusalem-Pilate's dream-The Temple-Everything's alright - I don't know how to love him - Damned for all time/Blood money - The Last Supper - Gethsemane (I only want to say) - The arrest - Peter's denial - Pilate and the Christ - King Herod's song (Tryit and see) - Judas's death - Trial before Pilate (Including the 39 lashes) - Supperstar - Crucifixion - John nineteen forty-one.
    - West Side Story: The Columbia Treasury of the American Musical Theatre, 1973 (Record HAMM SDT 0010)
      This album includes Prologue and Jet song (Orchestra; The Jets) - Something's coming (Larry Kert) - The dance at the GYM (Ensemble) - Maria (Larry Kert) - Tonight (Larry Kert, Carol Lawrence) - America (Chita Rivera and Marilyn Cooper, Reri Grist, & Shark Girls) - Cool (Mickey Calin and The Jets) - One hand, One heart (Larry Kert, Carol Lawrence) - Tonight (Quintet) (Ensemble) - The Rumble (Orchestra) - I feel pretty (Carol Lawrence, Marilyn Cooper, Carmen Guiterrez, Elizabeth Taylor) - Somewhere (Ballet) (Reri Grist and Ensemble) - Gee, Officer Krupke! (Eddie Roll, Grover Dale and The jets) - A boy like that (Carol Lawrence and Chita Rivera) - I have a love (Carol Lawrence and Chita Rivera) - Finale.
    - Rodgers and Hammerstein II: Oklahoma! (Original New York Production), 1958 (Record HAMM SDT 0011)
      This album includes Overture -- Oh, what a beautiful mornin' -- Surrey with the fringe on top -- Kansas City -- I can't say no -- Many a new day -- People will say we're in love -- Pore Jud is daid -- Out of my dreams -- All er nothin'--Oklahoma -- Finale.
    - Saturday Night Fever: The Original Movie sound Track, 1977 (Record HAMM SDT 0012)
      This album includes Stain' alive (Bee Gees) - How deep is your love (Bee Gees) - If I can't have you (Yvonne Elliman) - A fifth of Beethoven (Walter Murphy) - Jive talkin' (Bee Gees) - K-Jee (M.F.S.B.) - Calypso breakdown (Ralph Mac Donald) - More than a woman (Travares) - Night Fever (Bee Gees) - Boogie shoes (K. C. & The sunshine Band) - Disco inferno (The Trammps) - You should be dancing (Bee Gees) - Open sesame (Kool & The Gang) - More than a woman (Bee Gees) - Manhattan skyline - Night on disco mountain - Salsation (David Shire).
    - Breakin' (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack), 1984 (Record HAMM SDT 0013)
      This album includes Breakin'…There's no stopping us - Freakshow on the dance floor - Body work - 991/2 - Showdown - Heart of the beat - Street people - Cut it - Ain't nobody - Reckless.
    - Ed Sullivan Presents Porgy and Bess, 1959 (Record HAMM SDT 0014)
      This album includes Overture -- I got plenty o' nuttin' -- Bess you is my woman --Summertime -- Oh, Lawd, I'm on my way -- It ain't necessarily so -- I loves you, Porgy -- A woman is a sometime thing -- There's a boat dat's leavin' soon for New York -- My man's gone now.
    - Near You: The Andrews Sisters, 1958, 1959 (Record HAMM SDT 0015)
      This albm includes Near you (Francis Craig-Kermit Goell) - I don't know why (Ijust do) (Fred E. Ahlert-Roy Turk) - Sing a tropical song (Jimmy McHugh-Frank Loesser) - Daddy (Bob Troup) - I love you much toomuch (Don Raye-Alex Olshey-C.Towber) - She wore a yellow ribbon (M. Ottner) - A bushel and a peck (Frank Loesser) - How lucky you are (Eddie Cassen-Desmond O'Connor) - Carmen's boogie (George Cates-Mel Leven) - One for the woner (Sid Tepper-Roy Brodsky) - The blond sailor (J. Pfeil-Mitchell Parish-Bell Leib) - Charley my boy (Gus Kahn-Ted Fio Rito).
    - Henry Clay Work: Who Shall Rule this America Nation? - Songs of the Civil War, 1975 (Record HAMM SDT 0016)
      This album includes Who shall rule this American nation? (1:45) - Grafted inot the army (2:17) - Poor kitty popcorn, or the soldier's pet (3:22) - When the "Evening star" went down (3:22) - The Buckskin bag of gold (3:01) - "Come home father!" (4:56) - Uncle Joe's "Hail Columbia!" (2:30) - Grandfather's clock (3:26) - Kingdom coming (2:00) - The picture on the wall (3:25) - "Now, Moses!" (2:21) - Take them away --They'll drive me crazy (2:12) - Agnes by the river (3:29) - Crossing the Grand sierras (3:05) - The silver horn (5:36).
  - Ragtime, 1970-1980; XI.
    This series consists of seven albums. These albums represent the Popular American music of Ragtime.
    - Americana Vol. IV: The Age of Ragtime, 1974 (Record HAMM RAG 0001)
      This album includes "Harlem Rag" /Tom Turner (2:35) - "Possum and Taters" /Charles Hunter (3:15) - "Bohemia" Rag /Joseph Lamb (3:18) - "The Entertainer" /Scott Joplin (4:12) - "Maple Leaf rag" /Scott Joplin (3:05) - "Reflection rad" (Syncopated Musings) /Scott Joplin (4:25) - "Pastime Rag" No. 4 /Artie Matthews (2:15) - "Ragtime Oriole" /James Scott (3:44) - "Catact Rag" /Robert Hampton (3:23) - "Rialto Ripples" /George Gershwin and Will Donaldson (2:37) - "pork and Beans" /C. luckyth Roberts (1:59) - "Castle House rag" /James Reese Europe (2:54) - "Troublesome Ivories" (A Ragtime Rag) /j. Hubert Blake (2:09).
    - Heliotrope Bouquet: Piano Rags, 1971 (Record HAMM RAG 0002)
      This album includes A rag-time nightmare (March and two step) / Turpin (1:18) -- The easy winners (a ragtime two step) / Joplin (3:32) -- Heliotrope bouquet (a slow drag two step) / Joplin, Chauvin (4:05) -- Ethiopia rag / Lamb (3:38) -- Pegasus (a classic rag) / Scott (3:38) -- Wall Street rag / Joplin (4:16) -- Pork and beans (one step-two step or turkey trot) / Roberts (1:41) -- Graceful ghost / Bolcom (4:04) -- Seabiscuits / Bolcom (3:12) -- Brass knuckles / Albright, Bolcom (3:29).
    - John Hasse: Extraordinary Ragtime, 1980 (Record HAMM RAG 0003)
      This album includes Pine apple rag / Scott Joplin (3:31) -- The thriller rag / May Aufderheide (3:17) -- Frog legs rag / James Scott (2:38) -- Solace / Scott Joplin (5:34) -- Maple leaf rag / Scott Joplin (2:38) -- Alexander's ragtime band / Irving Berlin (2:10) -- Radiant rag / John Hasse (3:16) -- That demon rag / Russell Smith (3:34) -- Weeping willow / Scott Joplin (4:56) -- Hot house rag / Paul Pratt (2:35).
    - An Evening with Scott Joplin, 1972 (Record HAMM RAG 0004)
      This album includes Maple leaf rag (3:09) -- Solace: a Mexican serenade (6:14) -- The ragtime dance (4:25) -- Elite syncopations (3:01) -- Pleasant moments (3:17) --Pine apple rag (4:16) -- Bethena: a concert waltz (5:10) -- Magnetic rag (5:19) -- Excerpts from Treemonisha. The corn-huskers/We're goin' around (3:24); Good advice (4:56); A real slow drag (5:50); We're goin' around: (encore) (3:29).
    - Piano Rags by Scott Joplin (Joshua Rifkin), 1970 (Record HAMM RAG 0005)
      This album includes Maple leaf rag /1899 (3:13) - The entertainer /1902 (4:58) - The ragtime dance /1907 (3:13) - Gladiolus rag /1907 (4:24) - Fig leaf rag /1908 (4:36 - Scott Joplin's new rag /1912 (3:07) - Euphonic Sounds /1909 (3:53) - Magnetic rag /1914 (5:11).
    - Piano Rags by Scott Joplin (Joshua Rifkin), 1970 (Record HAMM RAG 0005.1)
      This album is a duplicate of HAMM RAG 0005.
    - Piano Roll Ragtime, 1970 (Record HAMM RAG 0006)
      This album includes States rag medley no. 8 -- St. Louis rag / Tom Turpin -- Maple leaf rag / Scott Joplin -- Possum and taters / Charles Hunter -- Jungle time / Phillip Severin -- Grace and beauty / James Scott -- Stop time rag / Scott Joplin -- Pineapple rag / Scott Joplin -- Euphonic sounds / Scott Joplin -- Cascade / Scott Joplin -- Pickles and peppers / Adelaine Shepherd -- Something doing / Joplin-Hayden -- Red pepper rag / Henry Lodge -- Powder rag / Raymond Birch -- Kismet rag / Joplin-Hayden.
  - Radio, 1985; X.
    This series consists of one album. This album is a sound recording of a radio broadcast on Popular American music and Rock & Roll.
    - And This is Rock n Roll, 1985 (Record HAMM RAD 0001)
      This album includes Moondog house radio show (Mar. 22, 1952) --; The Space man --; Rock 'n' roll party radio show (Sept. 8, 1954) -- Big Beat rock 'n' roll dance party TV show (Sept. 23,1958) -- Big beat rock 'n' roll dance party TV show (June 30, 1957 --; Alan Freed's last good-bye to all his devoted fans (Nov. 23, 1959).
  - Popular, 1871-1999; IX.
    This series consists of 367 albums. These albums represent Popular American music dating back to 1871 with the majority of the recordings showcasing the 1960's-1970's.
    - ABBA: Greatest Hits, volume 2, 1979 (Record HAMM POP 0001)
      This album includes Gimme! Gimme! Gimme! -- Knowing me, knowing you -- Take a chance on me -- Money, money, money -- Rock me -- Eagle -- Angeleyes -- Dancing queen -- Does your mother know -- Chiquitita -- Summer night city -- I wonder -- The name of the game -- Thank you for the music.
    - Margie Adam, Songwriter, 1976 (Record HAMM POP 0002)
      This album includes Best friend -- Images -- Lost in inner space -- Rag bag -- Sweet friend of mine -- Beautiful soul -- I've got a fury -- After the drought -- Sleazy -- Would you like to tapdance on the moon?
    - !! Going Places!!, 1966 (Record HAMM POP 0003)
      This album includes Tijuana taxi -- I'm getting sentimental over you -- More and more amor -- Spanish flea -- Mae -- 3rd man theme -- Walk, don't run -- Felicia -- And the angels sing -- Cinco de mayo -- A walk in the Black Forest -- Zorba the Greek.
    - The Lonely Bull, 1962 (Record HAMM POP 0004)
      This album includes The lonely bull = El solo toro -- El lobo = The wolf -- Tijuana sauerkraut -- Desafinato -- Mexico -- Never on Sunday -- Struttin' with Maria -- Let it be me -- Acapulco -- Limbo rock -- Crawfish -- A quiet tear = Lagrima quieta.
    - Sounds like Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass, 1966 (Record HAMM POP 0005)
      This album includes Gotta lotta livin' to do -- Lady Godiva -- Bo-bo -- Shades of blue -- In a little Spanish town -- Wade in the water -- Town without pity -- The charmer -- Treasure of San Miguel -- Miss Frenchy Brown -- Casino Royale.
    - SRO, 1966 (Record HAMM POP 0006)
      Scope and COntent Notes
      This album includes Mexican road race / S. Lake -- Bean bag /J. Pisano, J. Wechter, H. Alpert -- The Wall Street rag / B. Coleman -- For Carlos / J. Pisano, N. Ceroli, H. Alpert -- Blue Sunday / J. Wechter -- Freight train Joe / J. Pisano -- Our day will come / B. Hilliard, M. Garson -- The lonely bull; Crea mi amor; The Mexican shuffle; Green peppers / S. Lake -- Spanish flea / J. Wechter -- Tijuana taxi / B. Coleman -- So what's new? / P. Lee, J. Pisano.
    - America, 1871 (Record HAMM POP 0007)
      This album includes Riverisde / Bunnell (3:02) - Sandman / Bunnell (5:03) - Three roses / Bunnell (3:54) - Children / Bunnell (3:07) - A horse with no name / (4:10) - Here / Beckley (5:30) - I need you / Beckley (3:04) - Rainy day / Peek (3:00) - Never found the time / Peek (3:50) - Clarice / Beckley (4:00) - Donkey jaw / Peek (5:17) - Pigeon song / Bunnell (2:17).
    - Homecoming, 1972 (Record HAMM POP 0008)
      This album includes Ventura Highway -- To each his own -- Don't cross the river -- Moon song -- Only in your heart -- Till the sun comes up again -- Cornwall blank -- Head & heart -- California revisited -- Saturn nights.
    - American Hot Wax, 1978 (Record HAMM POP 0009)